Department of Computer Science Technical Reports 1985-1995: Finding Aid
Engineering Library
- Scheduling Data-Flow Graphs via Retiming and Unfolding, 1992 October; Report No.CS-TR-396-92; Chao, Liang-Fang; Sha, Edwin Hsing-Mean; 1 item
- DUEL- A Very High-Level Debugging Language, 1992 November; Report No.CS-TR-399-92; Golan, Michael; Hanson, David R.; 1 item
- A Closed Form Expression for the Form Factor between Two Polygons, 1993 January; Report No.CS-TR-404-93; Hanrahan, Pat; Schroder, Peter; 1 item
- Bibliography of Technical Reports 1985-91, 1993 January; Report No.CS-TR-405-93; Davies, Rebecca; 1 item
- Hash-consing Garbage Collection, 1993 February; Report No.CS-TR-412-93; Appel, Andrew W.; Goncalves, Marcelo J.R.; 1 item
- Clustering-Based Optimization Algorithm in Zero-Skew Routings, 1993 March; Report No.CS-TR-416-93; Edahiro, Masato; 1 item
- Depth Reduction for Noncommutative Arithmetic Circuits ( Extended Abstract), 1993 March; Report No.CS-TR-417-93; Allender, Eric; Jiao, Jia; 1 item
- A First-Order Isomorphism Theorem, 1993 March; Report No.CS-TR-418-93; Allender, Eric; Balcazar, Jose; 1 item
- Confluently Persistent Deques via Data-Structural Bootstrapping, 1993 March; Report No.CS-TR-420-93; Bushbaum, Adam L.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- A Catalog of Higher Paris and their Configuration Spaces, 1993 June; Report No.CS-TR-424-93; Joskowicz, Leo; Sacks, Elisha; 1 item
- Relationships among PL, #L, and the Determinant, 1993 June; Report No.CS-TR-425-93; Allender, Eric; Ogiwara, Mitsunori; 1 item
- A Uniform Circuit Lower Bound for the Permanent, 1993 June; Report No.CS-TR-426-93; Allender, Eric; Gore, Vivek; 1 item
- Evenly Distributed Depth is the Worst for Distributed Snooping, 1993 June; Report No.CS-TR-427-93; Cox, Michael; Hanrahan, Pat; 1 item
- Functional Algorithm Simulation: Implementation and Experiments, 1993 June; Report No.CS-TR-429-93; Dikaiakos, Marios D.; Rogers, Anne; Steiglitz, K.; 1 item
- Static Scheduling for Synthesis of DSP Algorithms on Various Models, 1993 August; Report No.CS-TR-432-93; Chao, Liang-Fang; Sha, Edwin Hsing-Mean; 1 item
- Unbeatable Benchmarks Using Numerical Instability, 1993 September; Report No.CS-TR-433-93; Ar, Sigal; Cai, Jin-yi; 1 item
- A Randomized Linear-Time Algorithm for FInding Minimum Spanning Trees, 1993 October; Report No.CS-TR-436-93; Klein, Phillip A.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Virtual Memory Mapped Network Interface for the SHRIMP Multicomputer, 1993 November; Report No.CS-TR-437-93; Alpert, Richard; Blumrich, Matthias A.; Dubnicki, Cezary; Felten, Edward W.; Li, Kai; Sandberg, Jonathan S.; 1 item
- Processes Capturing, 1993 November; Report No.CS-TR-439-93; Iftode, Liviu; Li, Kai; 1 item
- A Critical Analysis of Multigrid Methods on Massively Parallel Computers, 1993 December; Report No.CS-TR-440-93; Matheson, Lesley R.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Compression Performance of the Xremote Protocol, 1994 January; Report No.CS-TR-441-94; Danskin, John; Hanrahan, Pat; 1 item
- Profiling the X Protocol, 1994 January; Report No.CS-TR-442-94; Danskin, John; Hanrahan, Pat; 1 item
- Computing the Rectangle Discrepancy, 1994 January; Report No.CS-TR-443-94; Dobkin, David P.; Gunopulos, Dimitrios; 1 item
- Application-Controlled File Caching Policies, 1994 January; Report No.CS-TR-445-94; Cao, Pei; Felten, Edward W.; Li, Kai; 1 item
- Comparison Study of Heuristics for Mapping Parallel Algorithms to Message-Passing Multiprocessors, 1994 February; Report No.CS-TR-446-94; Dikaiakos, Marios D.; Rogers, Anne; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Supporting Dynamic Data Structures on Distributed Memory Machines, 1994 February; Report No.CS-TR-447-94; Carlisle, Martin C.; Hendren, Laurie J.; Reppy, John H.; Rogers, Anne; 1 item
- A Critical Analysis of Multigrid Methods on Massively Parallel Computers, 1994 February; Report No.CS-TR-448-94; Matheson, Lesley R.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Textures and Radiosity: Controlling Emission and Reflection with Texture Maps, 1994 March; Report No.CS-TR-449-94; Gershbein, Reid; Hanrahan, Pat; Schroder, Peter; 1 item
- Empirical and Analytical Study of Stack vs. Heap Cost for Languages with Closures, 1994 March; Report No.CS-TR-450-94; Appel, Andrew W.; Shao, Zhong; 1 item
- Axiomatic Bootstrapping: A Guide for Compiler Hackers, 1994 March; Report No.CS-TR-451-94; Appel, Andrew W.; 1 item
- Separate Compilation for Standard ML, 1994 March; Report No.CS-TR-452-94; Appel, Andrew W.; MacQueen, David B.; 1 item
- Unrolling Lists, 1994 March; Report No.CS-TR-453-94; Appel, Andrew W.; Reppy, John H.; Shao, Zhong; 1 item
- Space Efficient Closure Representations, 1994 March; Report No.CS-TR-454-94; Appel, Andrew W.; Shao, Zhong; 1 item
- Analysis of a Combined Hardware-Software Mechanism for Speculative Loads, 1994 April; Report No.CS-TR-455-94; Damianakis, Stefanos; Li, Kai; Rogers, Anne; 1 item
- Variational Modeling with Wavelets, 1994 April; Report No.CS-TR-465-94; Cohen, Michael F.; Gortler, Steven J.; 1 item
- Emulating Write-Allocate on a No-Write-Allocate Cache, 1994 June; Report No.CS-TR-459-94; Appel, Andrew W.; 1 item
- Linear-Work Parallel Algorithm for Finding Minimum Spanning Trees, 1994 May; Report No.CS-TR-457-94; Cole, Richard; Klein, Phillip A.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Loop Headers in λ- calculus or CP, 1994 June; Report No.CS-TR-460-94; Appel, Andrew W.; 1 item
- Dominating Sets in Planar Graphs, 1994 June; Report No.CS-TR-461-94; Matheson, Lesley R.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Implementation and Performance of Application-Controlled File Caching, 1994 June; Report No.CS-TR-462-94; Cao, Pei; Felten, Edward W.; Li, Kai; 1 item
- Where is Time Spent in Message-Passing and Shared-Memory Programs?, 1994 July; Report No.CS-TR-463-94; Chandra, Satish; Larus, James R.; Rogers, Anne; 1 item
- Application-Specific Protocols for User-Level Shared Memory, undated; Report No.CS-TR-464-94; Falsafi, Babak; Hill, Mark D.; Larus, James R.; Lebeck, Alvin R.; Reinhardt, Steven K.; Rogers, Anne; Schoinas, Ioannis; Wood, David A.; 1 item
- Computing the Maximum Bichromatic Discrepancy, with Applications to Computer Graphics and Machine Learning, 1994 October; Report No.CS-TR-467-94; Dobkin, David P.; Gunopulos, Dimitrios; Maass, Wolfgang; 1 item
- Collusion-Secure Fingerprinting for Digital Data, 1994 October; Report No.CS-TR-468-94; Boneh, Dan; Shaw, James; 1 item
- The New Jersey Machine-Code Toolkit, 1994 October; Report No.CS-TR-469-94; Fernandez, Mary; Ramsey, Norman; 1 item
- New Jersey Machine-Code Toolkit Architecture Specifications, 1994 October; Report No.CS-TR-470-94; Fernandez, Mary; Ramsey, Norman; 1 item
- New Jersey Machine-Code Toolkit Reference Manual Version 0.1, 1994 October; Report No.CS-TR-471-94; Fernandez, Mary; Ramsey, Norman; 1 item
- Probability Value Library, 1994 October; Report No.CS-TR-472-94; Ristad, Eric Sven; Yianilos, Peter N.; 1 item
- Sample and Effective Link-Time Optimization of Modula-3 Programs, 1994 November; Report No.CS-TR-474-94; Fernandez, Mary; 1 item
- Programmable Parallel Arithmetic in Cellular Automata Using a Particle Model, 1994 December; Report No.CS-TR-478-94; Squier, Richard; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Making Lambda Calculus Smaller, Faster, 1994 November; Report No.CS-TR-477-94; Appel, Andrew W.; Jim, Trevor T.Y.; 1 item
- A Study of Integrated Prefetching and Caching Strategies, 1994 December; Report No.CS-TR-479-94; Cao, Pei; Felten, Edward W.; Karlin, Anna R.; Li, Kai; 1 item
- The Maximum Discrepancy of Simple Geometric Ranges, 1994 December; Report No.CS-TR-480-94; Dobkin, David P.; Gunopulos, Dimitrios; 1 item
- Concept Learning with Simple Geometric Hypotheses, 1994 December; Report No.CS-TR-481-94; Dobkin, David P.; Gunopulos, Dimitrios; 1 item
- Cache Performance of Fast-Allocating Programs, 1994 December; Report No.CS-TR-482-94; Appel, Andrew W.; Goncalves, Marcelo J.R.; 1 item
- Software Caching and Computation Migration in Olden, 1995 January; Report No.CS-TR-483-95; Carlisle, Martin C.; Rogers, Anne; 1 item
- General Parallel Computation without CPUs: VLSI Realization of a Particle Machine, 1995 February; Report No.CS-TR-484-95; Jakubowski, Mariusz; Squier, Richard; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Nonmonotonic Multicontext Models, 1995 February; Report No.CS-TR-486-95; Ristad, Eric Sven; Thomas, J.B.; 1 item
- A Type-Based Complier for Standard ML, 1995 March; Report No.CS-TR-487-95; Appel, Andrew W.; Shao, Zhong; 1 item